{
    "id": "4bec3d94377947a19236897022bdc1ed",
    "title": "General Vocabulary Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I have ……………………….. respect for him.",
            "description": "Great is mainly used with abstract nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "big",
                "large",
                "great"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a12e8c29e1944217bc25c535e1d96a8c"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has got rather ………………………….. eyes.",
            "description": "Big and large are mainly used with concrete nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "big",
                "large",
                "great"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3d3f9a1aae894e4f88df4d3a9b0ffdb7"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………………….. a book from my sister.",
            "description": "We borrow something from somebody. Loan has a similar meaning. ",
            "answers": [
                "borrowed",
                "lent",
                "loaned"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a8d1e810d2974500a17afb6f051b2245"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………… me your pen for a minute, will you?",
            "description": "You lend something to somebody.",
            "answers": [
                "Lend",
                "Borrow"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ee2ea99e2bf74b1b8baba66edfd9616b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The job was hard but I …………………………… got used to it.",
            "description": "Soon means ‘a short time after then’.",
            "answers": [
                "soon",
                "early",
                "quickly"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "452fad42a99348ff8b7a877ef63857de"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………… that week, something suspicious occurred.",
            "description": "Early means near the beginning of the time period that we are talking or thinking about.",
            "answers": [
                "Soon",
                "Early",
                "Quickly"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9f38054190974e498d8df501d2ff4cdc"
        },
        {
            "question": "The train arrived 30 minutes ……………………………",
            "description": "Early means before the expected time.",
            "answers": [
                "soon",
                "early",
                "quickly"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3030cd4f16154cfea5c50cf19b3296e5"
        },
        {
            "question": "You are never ………………………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "early",
                "soon",
                "quickly"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6d9896ac39664ab1856484577341bf43"
        },
        {
            "question": "My watch is five minutes …………………………..",
            "description": "A watch or a clock can be fast or slow. ",
            "answers": [
                "slow",
                "late",
                "lately"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "291aabf2b9764ecaa7af962595caad6c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do something ……………………………. He is bleeding.",
            "description": "Quickly indicates the need to act urgently.",
            "answers": [
                "soon",
                "early",
                "quickly"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d4b5dc69298644efb08e9833d4be7fdc"
        },
        {
            "question": "Let’s meet ………………………………. next week.",
            "description": "Sometime means one day.",
            "answers": [
                "sometime",
                "some time",
                "some times"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "20ef20bef6f248188f60abefb98b5e9e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I’m afraid it will take ……………………………… to repair the car.",
            "description": "Some time means quite a lot of time.",
            "answers": [
                "sometime",
                "some time",
                "sometimes"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "810b01c4133e40f88d615aef592ba389"
        }
    ]
}